You're about to watch a video where people were protesting House Minority Leader
Hakeem Jeffries, who was speaking at a National Action Network event led by,
of course, Al Sharpton. The same Hakeem Jeffries who has received over $323,000
from the American Israel Public Affairs Committee, APAC, in just 2023 to 2024 alone.
I want you to just take notice of the way these people are treated.
All of this is happening in what's considered to be a black space.
A lot of these spaces are simply just black faces. But at the end of the day,
what does it mean morally, ethically? What is the value system at this point of a black space?
We got to really start asking these questions. I definitely have more to say about this. You can
comment and hear the rest of my thoughts at Patreon, Amanda Seals, or TheAmandaverse.com.